=Seal of Love= (Season 1)
= ختم الحب = (الموسم الأول)
=Episode 14=
= الحلقة 14 =
I don't believe you.
أنا لا أصدقك.
I'll go see my master.
سأذهب لرؤية سيدي.
Master,
يتقن،
Goddess Mu Yao said...
قالت الإلهة مو ياو ...
Fusheng,
فوشينغ ،
you hurt your fellow disciples.
لقد آذيت زملائك التلاميذ.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Master, you don't believe me?
سيدي ، أنت لا تصدقني؟
Naughty girl.
فتاة شقية.
Go get punished on the Immortal Spirit Platform
اذهب لتعاقب على منصة الروح الخالدة
until you know you're wrong.
حتى تعرف أنك مخطئ.
♪Our first meeting♪
لقائنا الأول
♪Was sealed by time♪
كانت مختومة بالزمن ♪
♪Who can I tell♪
♪ من أستطيع أن أقول
You're not afraid of death, fine.
أنت لا تخاف من الموت ، بخير.
What about Fusheng?
ماذا عن فوشينغ؟
Don't you care about her life either?
ألا تهتم بحياتها أيضًا؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Her demon core
جوهرها الشيطاني
is in my hand.
في يدي.
♪When memories appear♪
عندما تظهر الذكريات ♪
I dare you!
أتحداكم!
♪In the form of poets♪
على شكل شعراء ♪
♪Which one are you in♪
♪ في أي واحد أنت ♪
♪Year after year♪
♪ سنة بعد سنة
Qing Chen,
تشينغ تشن ،
if I die,
إذا مت ،
she dies, too.
انها تموت ايضا.
♪Bit by bit in a few nights♪
♪ شيئًا فشيئًا في بضع ليال ♪
♪I watch the stars flicker♪
♪ أشاهد النجوم تومض
♪You're too far away♪
♪ أنت بعيد جدا ♪
♪Why don't I dare to forget you♪
♪ لماذا لا أجرؤ على نسيانك
♪Letters by letters♪
حروف بحروف ♪
♪I weep as I write♪
أبكي وأنا أكتب ♪
♪Flowers and plants fade♪
♪ الزهور والنباتات تتلاشى ♪
♪In declining years♪
♪ في سنوات الانحدار ♪
♪Where will you be♪
♪ أين ستكون ♪
Wow, what a coincidence!
واو ، يا لها من مصادفة!
I often come here, too.
غالبًا ما آتي إلى هنا أيضًا.
As far as I remember,
بقدر ما اتذكر،
eating humble pie
أكل فطيرة متواضعة
is not exactly your temperament.
ليس بالضبط مزاجك.
The marriage of immortals
زواج الخالدين
can be very normal.
يمكن أن يكون طبيعيًا جدًا.
My master won't...
سيدي لن ...
In his eyes,
في عينيه،
you're just part of his life-saving plan.
أنت مجرد جزء من خطته المنقذة للحياة.
Fusheng,
فوشينغ ،
look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
No one but me
لا أحد سواي
makes a perfect couple with you.
يصنع زوجًا مثاليًا معك.
Qing Chen,
تشينغ تشن ،
your disciple is
تلميذك هو
quite unyielding.
عنيد جدا.
Master.
يتقن.
I'm taking you back.
سأعيدك.
Qing Chen!
تشينغ تشن!
If you dare to take her away now,
إذا كنت تجرؤ على أخذها بعيدًا الآن ،
I'll crush her core
سوف أسحق قلبها
and make her vanish.
وجعلها تختفي.
This is your only threat to me.
هذا هو التهديد الوحيد بالنسبة لي.
What else
ماذا بعد
can you get, then?
هل يمكنك الحصول عليه إذن؟
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
I've got plenty of time.
لدي متسع من الوقت.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You don't deserve to know my name.
أنت لا تستحق أن تعرف اسمي.
I've kept her core for quite a long time.
لقد احتفظت بجوهرها لفترة طويلة.
You think I didn't do anything on it?
هل تعتقد أنني لم أفعل أي شيء حيال ذلك؟
Stop trash-talking.
توقف عن الحديث عن القمامة.
Jing Yuan,
جينغ يوان ،
give her core to me.
أعطني جوهرها.
Time to give it back to her.
حان الوقت لردها لها.
Jing Yuan,
جينغ يوان ،
don't!
لا!
♪In the next life May everything be in peace♪
في الحياة الآخرة ، عسى أن يكون كل شيء في سلام
♪Back in the hometown Obsessions linger♪
♪ العودة في مسقط رأس الهواجس باقية ♪
♪Pursuing the skinny love I just can't get over it♪
♪ أسعى وراء الحب النحيف الذي لا يمكنني تجاوزه
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪
♪Dying together only exists in the legend♪
الموت معًا موجود فقط في الأسطورة
♪Memories fade away♪
الذكريات تتلاشى ♪
♪Why must I be heartbroken for someone merciless♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن أكون حزينة من أجل شخص لا يرحم
♪A perfect marriage appears in the dream♪
الزواج المثالي يظهر في الحلم ♪
♪But a dream ends anyway♪
♪ لكن الحلم ينتهي على أي حال
♪The wind blows The leaves fall Be away♪
تهب الرياح الأوراق تسقط كن بعيدًا ♪